[
  {
    "question": "How do the Fat-Eaters assert themselves at the beginning of Chapter 19 of Solar Storms?",
    "a": "They formally register with the Canadian government.",
    "b": "They sabotage the workers' gas station.",
    "c": "They dynamite a dam under construction.",
    "d": "They no longer allow outsiders to call them that name.",
    "e": "They make a treaty with the United States.",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does Bush attract suspicion among the protesters?",
    "a": "She slaps Arlie Caso House in anger.",
    "b": "She denounces her side's excesses.",
    "c": "She sells a newspaper an unflattering picture.",
    "d": "She writes an editorial for a hostile magazine.",
    "e": "She tries to talk to the police.",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does LaRue Marks Time draw the interest of young men protesting?",
    "a": "He is a veteran.",
    "b": "He is a sharp dresser.",
    "c": "He is fluent in five languages.",
    "d": "He is a medicinal elder.",
    "e": "He is a skilled hunter.",
    "correct_answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Tulik shut out the man in the suit who tries to negotiate in Chapter 19 of Solar Storms?",
    "a": "Tulik pronounces a curse on the man to his face.",
    "b": "Tulik serves the man a trespass notice.",
    "c": "Tulik leaves and lets Auntie negotiate.",
    "d": "Tulik turns off his hearing aid.",
    "e": "Tulik declares the man is not a man at all.",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "The burning of Tulik's house destroys all of the following objects EXCEPT",
    "a": "Tulik's salmon-skin coat",
    "b": "Ek's book of plants",
    "c": "Agnes's bearskin coat",
    "d": "Tulik's sealskin clothes",
    "e": "Luce's magnifying glass",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "To take revenge on the police and soldiers' food supplies, Angel",
    "a": "lights a building on fire",
    "b": "embodies Wolverine",
    "c": "flirts with the quartermaster",
    "d": "laces flour with cyanide",
    "e": "drugs the coffee",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does LaRue leave the protest site in Chapter 19 of Solar Storms?",
    "a": "He walks across the national border.",
    "b": "He flies out with Angel and Aurora.",
    "c": "He is carried away by a landslide.",
    "d": "He paddles a canoe away at midnight.",
    "e": "He steals a police car and drives it home.",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is Mr. Orensen the one to drive Bush, Angel, and Aurora out of the protest zone?",
    "a": "He created the shortcut that will get them to safety.",
    "b": "He is the only one with a working vehicle.",
    "c": "He believes the soldiers will not harm him.",
    "d": "He has already bribed the sergeant to let them pass.",
    "e": "He will not raise suspicion at checkpoints.",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Chapter 20 of Solar Storms, Bush grieves MOST prominently through",
    "a": "hunting",
    "b": "babysitting",
    "c": "cleaning",
    "d": "fishing",
    "e": "running",
    "correct_answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "On Fur Island, the rising waters float the skeleton of a(n)",
    "a": "eagle",
    "b": "bear",
    "c": "raven",
    "d": "wolverine",
    "e": "turtle",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  },
  {
    "question": "In Chapter 20 of Solar Storms, LaRue Marks Time cries for all of the following reasons EXCEPT",
    "a": "his war experiences",
    "b": "a dead animal",
    "c": "his own life",
    "d": "his lost house",
    "e": "Angel",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "The first setting in Chapter 21 of Solar Storms is",
    "a": "post-apocalyptic",
    "b": "urban",
    "c": "flooded",
    "d": "dreaming",
    "e": "abandoned",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does Tulik have his hair cut in Chapter 21 of Solar Storms?",
    "a": "He is making an offering to water.",
    "b": "He has singed it in a fire.",
    "c": "He is donating to his wife.",
    "d": "He wants to be taken seriously in court.",
    "e": "He is grieving a terrible loss.",
    "correct_answer": "d"
  },
  {
    "question": "How does Angel receive the summons to attend Dora-Rouge's death?",
    "a": "She meets a message runner at her door.",
    "b": "She gets a card in the mail.",
    "c": "She dreams Dora-Rouge tells her.",
    "d": "She answers a telephone call.",
    "e": "She receives a Western Union telegram.",
    "correct_answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dora-Rouge's manner of death is",
    "a": "agonized",
    "b": "wheezing",
    "c": "mysterious",
    "d": "lonely",
    "e": "peaceful",
    "correct_answer": "e"
  }
]